achievethecore.org 2019-04-24

# Achievethecore.org ::

  * Updates

We may change the terms of this Privacy Statement from time to time by posting an updated version on Our Site (or by other method of notice that we determine is appropriate). By continuing to use Our Site after we have given notice of the changed terms, you agree to the updated Privacy Statement; if you do not agree, you may not use Our Site. 

  * Collection and Use of Personal Information

We may collect personally identifiable information (e.g., name, email address, role, and school) (“Personal Information”)) when you voluntary provide it to us (e.g., to sign up for email). We use your Personal Information for the purposes for which you provide it. We may also send you information from SAP or third parties that we think may be of interest to you (e.g., information about newly available features or SAP activities). 

  * Other Information and Cookies

To help us improve the operation and usability of Our Site, we may also collect other information when you visit Our Site, such as IP address (i.e., the number assigned to a visitor’s computer to identify its location on the Internet), web pages viewed, time and date of visits to Our Site, the first page viewed upon arrival on Our Site, actions taken during a visit to Our Site (e.g., links clicked), the web site that referred or linked you to Our Site, and web browser used. 

Some parts of Our Site rely on cookies, which are small data files placed on your computer (or we may rely on other technology methods in the future). We use information collected by cookies to facilitate your use of Our Site. For example, cookies (or other methods) help make certain parts of Our Site work properly. You are not required to accept cookies from Our Site. You can disable the cookies function (or delete existing cookies) using your web browser’s options, although some functions of Our Site may not work properly if you do so. 

  * Sharing Information with Third Parties

We will share your Personal Information only with our service providers that help us operate Our Site (such as hosting or email providers). We reserve the right to disclose and use Personal Information and other information: to enforce this Privacy Statement or our Terms, to take action regarding suspected illegal activities; to protect the rights, safety or property of any one; to comply with legal process (e.g., a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order); to carry out a merger or consolidation with another entity or in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets or a similar transaction; or for other reasons we determine in good faith are necessary, appropriate, or required by law. 

  * Review and Correction of Personal and Other Information; Opt Out

If you wish to change Personal Information provided to us or if you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you can follow the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions in the materials you receive or email us at [info@studentsachieve.net](mailto:info@studentsachieve.net) (although we reserve the right to contact you in circumstances such as notices concerning changes to our Terms). 

  * Security

We strive to keep your Personal Information secure and to safeguard it from unauthorized access. Of course, no security measure can be guaranteed to be 100% effective, so you provide your Personal Information at your own risk. 

  * Persons under Age 13

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from persons under age 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and you believe that your child under age 13 may have provided personally identifiable information through Our Site, please email us at [info@studentsachieve.net](mailto:info@studentsachieve.net). 

  * Location of Servers and Transfer of Information

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using Our Site or providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to this transfer and to the collection, storage, processing and use of your Personal Information in the United States. 

  * Links to Third-Party Web Sites, including Social Networks

Our Site may contain links to third-party web sites and content providers which may interest you. If you follow any link to a third-party site, you leave Our Site. You should review those sites’ privacy statements to find out how they treat your information. 

  * Questions

Please email us at [info@studentsachieve.net](mailto:info@studentsachieve.net) if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement.
